{
    "id": "994287ce39f64165a9e11d685bd03dab",
    "title": "Intermediate Level Grammar Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "I am not used to …………….. alone.",
            "description": "Be used to can be followed by nouns or ing forms. It cannot be followed by infinitives.",
            "answers": [
                "live",
                "living",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "81ca2abdbd084c3cb5c8e465a733171f"
        },
        {
            "question": "It took me quite some time to ……………… living in a big city.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "get used to",
                "get use to",
                "got used to"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "9db1817ade114861a5f2b757ecea4c41"
        },
        {
            "question": "I ……………… very hard last month.",
            "description": "We do not use ‘used to’ to simply say what happened at a past time. That idea is expressed using the simple past. ",
            "answers": [
                "worked",
                "used to work",
                "used to working"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "9d26f9faecfc492daec034eb85a26d9b"
        },
        {
            "question": "A minibus can hold ……………….. fifteen people.",
            "description": "We use until to talk about time. To talk about quantity and distance, we use up to.",
            "answers": [
                "up to",
                "until",
                "till"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "afb8e6a0e1ab49d1a7a435c7949522dd"
        },
        {
            "question": "Can you repair my camera if I leave it ……………… Friday?",
            "description": "We use until to talk about a situation that will continue up to a certain moment. By is used to say that an action will happen at or before a future moment.",
            "answers": [
                "until",
                "up to",
                "by"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "55af9c48cf3649cb9b6bf1e0a323c5e9"
        },
        {
            "question": "Can I stay with you ……………. Monday?",
            "description": "We use until to talk about a situation that will continue up to a certain moment. By is used to say that an action will happen at or before a future moment. Up to is used to indicate distance and quantity. ",
            "answers": [
                "up to",
                "until",
                "by"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "189fb60bd914434b9cb9828be55dcf41"
        },
        {
            "question": "You have to leave …………….. Tuesday midday at the latest.",
            "description": "By is used to say that an action will happen at or before a future moment.",
            "answers": [
                "until",
                "up to",
                "by"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "119ba5713a904b1f8884ed4c13306de8"
        },
        {
            "question": "The nearest restaurant is about half a kilometer …………….. the road.",
            "description": "In this case both up and down can be used to mean ‘along’ with no difference of meaning.",
            "answers": [
                "up",
                "down",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "90e321f8003e4b37b2ba7558270dc283"
        },
        {
            "question": "One cannot help ……………….. his courage.",
            "description": "'Cannot help but + infinitive' can be used with the meaning of ‘can’t help…ing’",
            "answers": [
                "but admire",
                "admiring",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "a021747f85454d2880b80d9223f2d86d"
        },
        {
            "question": "……………… I become a billionaire, I will always lead a simple life.",
            "description": "Even if refers to the future. Even though refers to the past. Even cannot be used as a conjunction.",
            "answers": [
                "Even if",
                "Even though",
                "Even"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "830ab1f3a2434a52bf62c9d9ae893407"
        },
        {
            "question": "The man ………………. she married was an old friend of mine.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "that",
                "whom",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "2ea39cffc6bf4021aa2edd0ec497bc84"
        },
        {
            "question": "I have been working …………….. morning and I am getting tired.",
            "description": "Since is normal with perfect and perfect continuous tenses. ",
            "answers": [
                "since",
                "from",
                "for"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "a37baa86651c4545bcdc692d53a5769d"
        }
    ]
}